Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Labor Movement Serials WAG.345
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Labor unions and organizations, 1891-2012; 188.25 Linear Feet in 24 record cartons and 139 oversize flat boxes
  - Subseries I.J: Public Employees, 1921-2005; 11 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 8 oversize flat boxes
    This series collects various uncataloged serials and newsletters mainly issued by large national organizations including the American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees; Civil Service Employees Association; Civil Service Employees Association; District Council 1707 Shop Stewards; New York State Department of Labor; and New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University. Weekly and monthly newsletters document union advocacy at a national scale, providing significant coverage of changes in labor law -- collective bargaining; retiree rights; strike actions -- as well as documenting the day-to-day circumstances of particular unions, for example the election of union representatives, and divisions between organizations and rank and file groups.
    - Princeton University Annual Giving: AG Staff at Princeton University, Princeton, NJ, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Contract Now!: American Federation of School Administrators (AFL-CIO) - Local 1, 1998 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Voice of 1707: American Federation of State, County & Municipal Employees, New York, NY, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 3, Box 79, Folder 1-5, Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Union News-Views: American Federation of State, County & Municipal Employees - Council 16, Middletown, CT, 1967 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Boycott Shell Bulletin: American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Washington, DC, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Weekly Report: American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Washington, DC, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - AFSCME/New York State: American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFL-CIO), Albany, NY, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Collective Bargaining Reporter: American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFL-CIO), Washington, DC, 1996-1997 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Retiree Rights: American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFL-CIO), Washington, DC, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Spotlight: American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1953, 1956-1959 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Women's Letter: American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFL-CIO), Washington, DC, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Legislative Action: American Labor Party, New York, NY, 1947 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - News: American Labor Party, New York, NY, circa 1950s (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Record: American Labor Party of New York State, New York, NY, 1948 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - New York Citizen: American Labor Party of NY County, New York, NY, 1939 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Arizona Professor: Arizona College and University Faculty Association, Phoenix, AZ, 1971 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Bulletin!: Associated Industries of New York State, Inc., Albany, NY, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Legislative News Letter: ASU-New York District, New York, NY, 1939 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Guidelines for AFT Involvement in Big City School Integration: Big City Locals of the American Federation of Teachers in Conference, Chicago, IL, 1963 (Box 172, Folder 33)
    - Sendout: Brooklyn Union Gas Employees, Brooklyn, NY, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Telephone Workers' News: Brotherhood of Utility Employees of America, New York, NY, 1936 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Service Union Reporter: California State Council of Service Employees (AFL-CIO), Los Angeles, CA, circa 1960s (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - California Pride: California State Employees Association, Sacramento, CA, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 18-21)
    - Labor Times: Chicago and Central States Joint Board, Chicago, IL, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Moving Forward: Chinese Staff and Workers' Association - Youth Group, New York, NY, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 22)
    - State of Our Union - CSEA 2006/2005 Legislative Summary: Civil Service Employees Association, New York, NY (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Essentially Women: Civil Service Employees Association, Inc. / Local 1000, Albany, NY, 1996-1998 (Box 74, Folder 23)
    - Public Sector: Civil Service Employees Association, Local 1000 (American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees), Albany, NY, 1990-1996 (Box 82, Folder 1-5, Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Civil Service Standard: Civil Service Standard, Inc., New York, NY, 1938 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Guild-Gram: Civil Service Technical Guild - Local 375, DC 37, New York, NY, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - Committee for Real Change in DC 37 (CRC): Committee for Real Change, District Council 37, Brooklyn, NY, 1999 (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - Rank and File Caucus Union News: Committee of Concerned State Workers, New York, NY, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 26)
    - CPSR Newsletter: Computer Professionals for Social Responsibility, Palo Alto, CA, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 27)
    - DC 1707 Street Heat: DC 1707 AFSCME, 2000 (Box 74, Folder 28)
    - Voice: DC 1707 AFSCME, 1978, 1983, 1986-2005 (Box 77, Folder 1-5)
    - Union Women United: DC 37, Women's Committee, New York, NY, 1983 (Box 74, Folder 29)
    - How to Stop Sexual Harassment: DC 37's National Union (AFSCME), New York, NY, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Home Care Concerns: District Council 1707 - Local 389 and the Home Care Employees Health and Welfare Fund, New York, NY, 1993-1996 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Steward Leader: District Council 1707 Shop Stewards (American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees), New York, NY, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 30)
    - Local 1930 Newsline: District Council 37 (AFSCME, AFL-CIO) - New York Public Library Guild, New York, NY, 1987-1989 (Box 74, Folder 31)
    - Contract News: District Council 37 Locals 371, 420, 1549, circa 1970s (Box 74, Folder 32)
    - Minority Affairs: Division of Minority Affairs, Washington State University, Pullman, WA, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 33)
    - Education WOB: workers organizing bulletin: Education Workers Industrial Union 620, Cortland, NY, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 34)
    - FUSA Advocate: Florida United Service Association, Jacksonville, FL, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Local 200 Reporter: General Service Employees Union (AFL-CIO) - Local 200, Syracuse, NY, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - GCEOC - CIO News: Government and Civic Employees Organizing Committee, CIO, New York, NY, 1953 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Voice of the Grand Council of Columbia Associations in Civil Service: Grand Council of Columbia Associations in Civil Service, New York, NY, 1965 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Illinois Labor: Illinois State Industrial Union Council, Chicago, IL, 1954 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - ISEA News: Indiana State Employees Association (ISEA), Indianapolis, IN, 1983-1987 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Legislative News/Legislative Newsbrief: Indiana State Employees Association (ISEA), Indianapolis, IN, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 35)
    - Newsbrief: Indiana State Employees Association (ISEA), Indianapolis, IN, 1983 (Box 74, Folder 36)
    - Sentinel: Indiana State Employees Association (ISEA), 1988-1989 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - News & Views: Institute for Food and Development Policy, Oakland, CA, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 37)
    - ISR Journal: Institute for Staff Relations and Governance at New York University, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 38)
    - Illinois Public Employee Relations Report: Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, Champaign, IL, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 39)
    - International Fire Fighter: International Association of Fire Fighters, Washington, DC, 1981-1986 (Box 78, Folder 1-2)
    - Police Chronicle: International Brotherhood of Police Officers, Quincy, MA, 1986-1996 (Box 78, Folder 3-4)
    - Bulletin: International Committee of Municipal Workers and Workers in Public Services, 1934 (Box 74, Folder 40)
    - Guard News: International Union, United Plant Guard Workers of America (UPGWA), Roseville, MI, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - IHEA Communique: Iowa Higher Education Association, Des Moines, IA, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 41)
    - Live-Wire: Live Wire, Los Angeles, CA, 1951 (Box 74, Folder 42)
    - New York Connection: Local 131, New York, NY, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 43)
    - Billboard Guildsman: Locked-Out Staff of the Billboard, New York, NY, 1946 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - R.A. Unionist: Lodge 206 AFGE, 1936 (Box 74, Folder 44)
    - Unionist: Lodge 206 AFGE, 1937 (Box 74, Folder 45)
    - Bargaining Update: Massachusetts Society of Professors Faculty Staff Union, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 46)
    - Bulletin: Members United for a Better Contract, A Coalition of Concerned APWU Members, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 47)
    - Local 44 Union News: Metro Tri-State Police Federation of Investigators and Security Trades (IUPA, AFL-CIO), 1982 (Box 74, Folder 48)
    - Michigan CIO News: Michigan State Industrial Council (CIO), Detroit, MI, 1948 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - School of Labor and Industrial Relations Newsletter: Michigan State University, East Lansing, MI, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 49)
    - Viewpoints MSLC: Missouri State Labor Council, Jefferson City, MO, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 50)
    - Amnesty Issue: N.Y. Metro Area Postal Union, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 51)
    - NAGE Reporter: National Association of Government Employees, Washington, DC, 1986-1996, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 2-3)
    - Manhattan Bronx Chapter #23: National Association of Retired Federal Employees, Floral Park, NY, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 52)
    - NFA Reports: National Education Association, Washington, DC, 1971-1972 (Box 172, Folder 31)
    - Federation News Service: National Federation of Post Office Clerks, Washington, DC, 1953-1956 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - NFSSE Forum: National Federation of Social Service Employees, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Mail Handler Exchange: National Postal Mail Handlers Union, Washington, DC, 1988-1989 (Box 74, Folder 53)
    - Local 300 Mail Handler News: National Postal Mail Handlers Union - Local 300 (AFL-CIO-CLC), New York, NY, 1995 (Box 74, Folder 54)
    - New Directions: New Directions Caucus of the UFT, New York, N.Y., 1976, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Civil Service Leader: New York City Civil Service Retired Employees Association, New York, NY, 1976 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Newsletter: New York City Department of Labor, Division of Labor Research, New York, NY, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 55)
    - Fed's News Flash: New York Federation of Post Office Clerks, New York, NY, 1954 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Universitas: New York State AFT College and University Council, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 56)
    - Labor Alert: New York State Assembly Labor Committee, Albany, NY, 2001 (Box 74, Folder 57)
    - Promises and Performance/Special Bulletin No. 3: New York State CIO, New York, NY, circa 1970s (Box 74, Folder 58)
    - Weekly News: New York State Council of Senior Citizens, New York, NY, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Jobs Hot-Line: New York State Department of Labor, Albany, NY, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 59)
    - Occupational Injuries and Illness Survey: New York State Department of Labor, Albany, NY, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 60)
    - Labor Bulletin: New York State Department of Labor - Office of Communication, Albany, NY, 1984, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 61)
    - Labor Research Report: New York State Department of Labor Division of Research and Statistics, Albany, NY, 1988 (Box 74, Folder 62)
    - Labor Organizations in New York State, 1955: New York State Department of Labor, Division of Research and Statistics, Albany, NY, 1956 (Box 74, Folder 63)
    - State Employee News: New York State Employees Council 50, Albany, NY, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Newsletter: New York State Labor Department, Albany, NY, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 64)
    - Renewing the Community, Celebrating Diversity: New York State Labor-Religion Coalition, Albany, NY, 1995 (Box 74, Folder 65)
    - News-Gram: New York State Legislative and Education Board, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Albany, NY, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 66)
    - Communicator: New York State Public Employees Federation, New York, NY, 1975, 1986-1987, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - PERB News: New York State Public Employment Relations Board, Albany, NY, 1968-1978 (Box 172, Folder 34-35)
    - Bulletin: New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 1955 (Box 74, Folder 67)
    - ILR Bulletin: New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 68)
    - ILR Reprints/ILR Reprint Series: New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, circa 1990s (Box 75, Folder 37-40)
    - Industrial and labor relations Report Card: New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 1972 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Labor Historians' Bulletin: New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University, Ithaca, NY, 1955, 1959 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - New York State Service Employee: New York State Service Employees Council (AFL-CIO), New York, NY, 1977-1979, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - 34&35 Local: News Committee, 1991 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Non-AC News: Nonacademic Workers of the University of Illinois, Urbana, IL, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Up From the Shadows: Northern States Co-Operative League, Minneapolis, MN, 1934 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Special Collections: Penn State Special Collections Department, University Park, PA, 1989, 1992-1993 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - On the Line: Police Benevolent Association, New York, NY, 1991-1994 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Detroit Area Postal Action: Postal Action Committee, Detroit, MI, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - P.O.W. (Post Office Worker): Postal Workers Defense Committee, New York, NY, 1979-1980 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - PSCcuny Newsletter: Professional Staff Conference of the City of New York, New York, NY, 2000 (Box 172, Folder 30)
    - The PSC Position on the CUNY Master Plan: Professional Staff Conference of the City of New York, New York, NY, circa 2000 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - PEF-ODDD Newsletter: Public Employees Federation Office of Disability Determinations Division, New York, NY, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Open Pouch: Railway Mail Association, New York, NY, 1945, 1948-1958 (Box 81, Folder 2-3)
    - Men and Ships: A Pictorial of the Maritime Industry: San Francisco Bay Area District Council No. 2, Maritime Federation of the Pacific Coast / Wobbers, Inc., San Francisco, CA, 1937 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Facts: Social Service Employees Union, New York, NY, 1967 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - SSEU News: Social Service Employees Union, New York, NY, 1965-1969 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Untitled newsletter: Social Service Employees Union - Local 371, New York, NY, circa 1970 (Box 172, Folder 32)
    - Campaigner: Social Service Employees Union - Local 371 Committee for New Leadership, New York, NY, 1973 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Labor Papers on Microfilm: State Historical Society of Wisconsin, Madison, WI, 1965 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Association Advocate: State of Nevada Employees Association, Carson City, NV, 1990-1991 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Directory of Labor Organizations in New York State 1955: State of New York - Department of Labor Division of Research and Statistics, New York, NY (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Industrial Code Bulletin: State of New York Department of Labor, Albany, NY, circa 1930s (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Special Bulletin: State of New York Department of Labor, 1928 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Weekly Legislative Digest: State of New York Department of Labor, New York, NY, 1951, 1954 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Working: State of New York Department of Labor, Albany, NY, 1994 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Employee: State, County and Municipal Workers of America, Washington, DC, 1938 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Newsletter: Statewide Coalition for a Democratic Union (SCDU), Albany, NY, 1980 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Is It Still Okay to Hate Al Shanker?: Sterling Lord Agency, Inc./UFT, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Affinities: SUNY State Education Department/Office of Cultural Education, Albany, NY, 1991-1994 (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Election of officers of labor organizations: U.S. Department of Labor, 1959 (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Guide to the National Labor Relations Act: U.S. Department of Labor: Division of Labor Standards, Washington, DC, 1946 (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - Fire Lines: Uniformed Firefighters Association, New York, N.Y., 1960, 1970-1975, 1978, 1984-1986 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - UCATS Momentum: Union of Clerical, Administrative, & Technical Staff (UCATS) at NYU, Local 3882, New York, NY, 2007 (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - Union News: Union of State Employees - Local 382, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - New Action Coalition of the UFT: United Federation of Teachers, Glen Oaks, New York, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 27)
    - Post Office Clerk: United National Association of Post Office Clerks, Washington, DC, 1951 (Box 75, Folder 28)
    - Career / United Office and Professional Workers of America: United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA), New York, NY, 1949 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Guild News/Book and Magazine Guild Bulletin: United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA) - Local 18, New York, NY, 1937-1938 (Box 75, Folder 29)
    - Social Service Employees Union News: United Office and Professional Workers of America (UOPWA) - Local 19, New York, NY, 1941 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Labor Offices in the United States and in Canada: United States Department of Labor, Washington, DC, 1945 (Box 75, Folder 30)
    - Monthly Report: United States Department of Labor, 1955-1956 (Box 75, Folder 31)
    - Women's Bureau Bulletin - Women at Work: United States Department of Labor - Women's Bureau, Washington, DC, 1934 (Box 75, Folder 32)
    - News: United States Department of Labor Bureau of Labor Statistics, Washington, DC, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 33)
    - Labor Party News: United States Labor Party, New York, NY, 1936 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - University Guardian: University Council, Berkeley, CA, 1971-1972 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Union News and Views: University of Wisconsin Employees Union - Local 171, Madison, WI, 1988 (Box 172, Folder 55)
    - American Workplace: US Department of Labor, Washington, DC, 1994-1995 (Box 75, Folder 34)
    - Local 1-2 - 2004 Contract: Utility Workers Union of America, New York, NY (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Gas Flame: Utility Workers Union, Local 142, CIO, Brooklyn, NY, 1940 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Voice of 743: Warehouse/Mail order/Office/Technical & Professional Employees Union - Local 743, Chicago, IL, 1978, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 35)
    - Labor history: Wayne State University, Detroit, MI, 1999 (Box 75, Folder 36)
    - Outlaw: Written by Postal Workers for Postal Workers -- Local (unintelligible), 1972-1976, undated (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Subseries I.K: Retail and Service Workers, 1891-2010; 34 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons and 26 oversize flat boxes
    The serials in this series document the activities of unions of clothing workers, retail staff, hospital housestaff, and hotel and food service employees. Among the publishing organizations represented are large, national unions including the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. The series contains newspapers and newsletters documenting textile work in and around New York throughout the 20th Century, including serials aimed at younger readers -- the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union's Student Magazine -- and three variants of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union's newspaper Justice: the Italian-language Giustizia, the Yiddish-language Gerechtigkeit, and the Spanish-language Justicia).
    - Union Builder: Advance, 1937 (Box 49, Folder 50)
    - Nor'easter: Amalgamated Northeast Regional Joint Board, UNITE, New York, NY, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 51)
    - Union Leader: Amalgamated Association of Street Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees, Chicago, IL, 1942 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Actor Unity: Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Organization of Retirees, New York, NY, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 52)
    - ACTWU Labor: Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, AFL-CIO, CLC, New York, NY, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 53)
    - ACTWU Songbook: Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, AFL-CIO, CLC, New York, NY, circa 1970s (Box 49, Folder 54)
    - How the Union Works: Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, AFL-CIO, CLC, New York, NY, circa 1970s (Box 49, Folder 48)
    - J.P. Stevens Boycott News: Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, AFL-CIO, CLC, Boston, MA, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - A Stitch in Time...: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1950 (Box 49, Folder 55)
    - Advance: Official Organ of the ACWA: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, New York, NY, 1936, 1954, 1969, 1974-1976 (Box 58, Folder 4-7)
    - Be Wise - Organize!: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, New York, NY, circa 1970s (Box 49, Folder 56)
    - In The Public Interest: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 57)
    - Needle and Thread: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, circa 1950s (Box 49, Folder 58)
    - Welfare Program: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 59)
    - Mimeo Handbook: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - National Department of Education, New York, NY, 1950 (Box 49, Folder 49)
    - Farah Strike News: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, AFL-CIO, US, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Book of the Amalgamated in New York 1914-1940: Amalgamated Joint Boards and Local Unions in New York, New York, NY (Box 172, Folder 37)
    - 174 News: Amalgamated Meat-Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Bronx, NY, 1971 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Forefront: Amalgamated Meatcutters and Retail Food Store Employees Union, US, 2001 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - New Textile Worker: Amalgamated Textile Workers of America, 1919 (Box 162, Folder 17)
    - Investigate the Communist Administration of the Furriers Union: American Federation of Fur Workers, New York, NY, 1940 (Box 172, Folder 39)
    - Silk Worker: Associated Silk Workers of America, Paterson, NJ, 1929 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - ABSW Newsletter: Association of Black Social Workers, New York, NY, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - B&C News: Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America, Washington, DC, 1968-1972, 1976-1977, 1981-1982, 1984, 1986, 1991-1994 (Box 61, Folder 1-5)
    - Bakers' and Confectioners' Journal: Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America, Chicago, IL, 1945 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Local 50 News: Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America, Local 50, New York, NY, 1970, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - BC&T Report: Bakery, Confectionery and Tobacco Workers International Union, Washington, DC, 1979-1981, 1989, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - BC&T News / Bakery, Confectionery, and Tobacco Workers International Union: Bakery, Confectionery, and Tobacco Workers International Union, Washington, DC, 1978-1982, 1996-1997 (Box 61, Folder 6-8)
    - BCTGM Communicator: Bakery, Confectionery, Tobacco and Grain Millers Union, circa 1990s (Box 60, Folder 7-9, Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Union Barman: Bartenders Union of New York City, New York, NY, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Local 140: Bedding, Curtain & Drapery Workers Union, New York, NY, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Ticker Tape: Bookkeepers', Stenographers' and Accountants Union - Wall Street Division, New York, NY, 1937 (Box 172, Folder 69)